Guide to the David Burge Papers MSS.395
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Media, Burge, David, 1930-2013
  - Sound recordings- Originals
    - Music by David Burge, Vol. XX - Dances of Love and Laughter, 2001; ID: 395.0032; Original format: CD (Box 18, Media ID: 395.0032)
    - Five Chromatic Dances; The Dream Rags - William Albright, undated; ID: 395.0033; Original format: CD (Box 18, Media ID: 395.0033)
    - Oh Sorrow, Sing Sorrow, final copy, 2006; ID: 395.0034; Original format: CD (Box 18, Media ID: 395.0034)
    - Preludes; Luna Lunera - David Burge1, undated; ID: 395.0035; Original format: CD (Box 18, Media ID: 395.0035)
    - Rainbows; Kaleidoscope - David Burge, undated; ID: 395.0036; Original format: CD (Box 18, Media ID: 395.0036)
    - Reminiscence - David Burge, 2005; ID: 395.0037; Original format: CD (Box 18, Media ID: 395.0037)
    - Sonata for Violin and Piano - David Burge, 1999; ID: 395.0038; Original format: CD (Box 18, Media ID: 395.0038)
- Series VII: Objects
  - Eastman School of Music Piano Diploma, 1956 (Box 16)
  - Music Teachers National Association plaque, 1977 (Box 16)
  - National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences - Best classical performance nomination plaque, 1974 (Box 16)
  - University of Rochester - Doctor of Musical Arts diploma, 1956 (Box 16)
- Oversize Series I: Scores
  - Burge Scores - Sources II (CHAMBER), 1965 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Sources III (CHAMBER), 1967 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Aeolian Music (CHAMBER), 1968 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - String Quartet (CHAMBER), 1969 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Viola Sonata "Azaleas" (CHAMBER), 2005 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Emma's Day (CHAMBER), 2006 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Improvisations (PIANO), 1953 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Third Piano Sonata (PIANO), 1959 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Sources IV (PIANO), 1969 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Go-Hyang (PIANO), 1984 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - 24 Preludes (PIANO), 1996 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Rainbows (PIANO), 2003 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Portami il Girasole (VOCAL), 1957 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Gloria del distresso mezzogiorno (VOCAL), 1985 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Songs of Love and Sorrow (VOCAL), 1989 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Candytata (VOCAL), 1998 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Sonatina (VIOLIN), 1960 (Box 19)
  - Burge Scores - Serenade (VIOLIN), 1960 (Box 20)
  - Burge Scores - Liana's Song (VARIOUS), 1995 (Box 20)
  - Burge Scores - When Love Prevails (VIBRAPHONE), 2002 (Box 20)
  - Burge Scores - Piano Concerto (ORCH, THEATER, DANCE), 1956 (Box 20)
  - Burge Scores - Variations on a Well-Known Tune (ORCH, THEATER, DANCE), 1958 (Box 20)
  - Burge Scores - Centennial Music (ORCH, THEATER, DANCE), 1959 (Box 20)
  - Burge Scores - Serenade (ORCH, THEATER, DANCE), 1960 (Box 20)
  - Burge Scores - "...that no one knew..." (ORCH, THEATER, DANCE), 1969 (Box 20)
  - Burge Scores - String Symposium examples (ORCH, THEATER, DANCE), 1968 (Box 21)
  - Burge Scores - La Loteria (ORCH, THEATER, DANCE), 1998 (Box 21)
  - Burge Scores - Twone in Sunshine (ORCH, THEATER, DANCE), 1969 (Box 21)
  - Performance Scores - Wourinen, Charles - Second Trio, 1962 (Box 21)
  - Performance Scores - Stockhausen, Karlheinz - Klavierstuck VIII, Undated (Box 22)
- Oversize Series VII: Objects
  - Korean Hanging Scrolls (2) from Young Hae's father, 1980 (Box 22)
- Oversize Series VIII: Posters and Artwork
  - "David Burge Conducting the Boulder Philharmonic Orchestra" posters, 1965-1971 (Box 21)
  - Denver Symphony Orchestra poster (2 copies), 1971 (Box 22)
  - Portrait of David Burge by G. Chang (poem taped to back), 1990 (Box 21)
  - "PVT David R. Burge, Accomplished Northwestern University Pianist, Piano Recital", 1953 (Box 21)
  - "Vanishing Spring" novel poster, Undated (Box 21)